A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Politics - George L. Hinman, Series J.2 FA346
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1960-1970; 1; 28.4 Cubic Feet
  - Kenner - Keyser (Box 30, Folder 178)
  - Khovaylo - Kindschy (Box 30, Folder 179)
  - King (Box 30, Folder 180)
  - King (Box 30, Folder 181)
  - Kingman - Kiser (Box 31, Folder 182)
  - Kissinger, Henry (Box 31, Folder 183)
  - Kissinger, Henry (Box 31, Folder 184)
  - Kleberg - Knight, Douglas (Box 31, Folder 185)
  - Knight, Goodwin (Box 31, Folder 186)
  - Knight, Jack - Koch (Box 31, Folder 187)
  - Koerkle - Kruse (Box 31, Folder 188)
  - Kuchel, Thomas (Box 32, Folder 189)
  - Kuehn - Kyle (Box 32, Folder 190)
  - K General (Box 32, Folder 0190A)
  - La Barbara - Lair (Box 32, Folder 191)
  - Laird, Melvin (Box 32, Folder 192)
  - Laiser - Lanigan (Box 32, Folder 193)
  - Lankler, Alexander M. (Box 32, Folder 194)
  - Lannon - Lauricella (Box 32, Folder 195)
  - Laverty - Lear (Box 32, Folder 196)
  - Learned - Leech (Box 33, Folder 197)
  - Leetham, Julius (Box 33, Folder 198)
  - Leetham, Julius (Box 33, Folder 199)
  - Lefferts - Levine (Box 33, Folder 200)
  - Levison - Lewsadder (Box 33, Folder 201)
  - Lianzi - Lindemer (Box 33, Folder 202)
  - Lindenbusch - Lindsay, James (Box 33, Folder 203)
  - Lindsay, John (Box 34, Folder 204)
  - Lindsay, Juan - Livingston (Box 34, Folder 205)
  - Lloyd - Lockwood (Box 34, Folder 206)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, George Cabot, & John David (Box 34, Folder 207)
  - Loeb - Lorne (Box 34, Folder 208)
  - Losee - Loy (Box 34, Folder 209)
  - Lublin - Lundy (Box 34, Folder 210)
  - Lunken - Lytle (Box 35, Folder 211)
  - L General (Box 35, Folder 0211A)
  - MacArthur - Mackey (Box 35, Folder 212)
  - Maclay - Mahoney (Box 35, Folder 213)
  - Mailing List (Box 35, Folder 214)
  - Maillard - Marchant (Box 35, Folder 215)
  - Marcus - Marston (Box 35, Folder 216)
  - Martin (Box 36, Folder 217)
  - Martin (Box 36, Folder 218)
  - Martindale - Mason (Box 36, Folder 219)
  - Massakas - Matthews (Box 36, Folder 220)
  - Mattox - Mazo (Box 36, Folder 221)
  - McAdam - McCart (Box 36, Folder 222)
  - McCarthy - McClay (Box 37, Folder 223)
  - McClellan - McDermott (Box 37, Folder 224)
  - McDade - McHose (Box 37, Folder 225)
  - McHugh (Box 37, Folder 226)
  - McInerny - McKendree (Box 37, Folder 227)
  - McKennett - McKneally (Box 37, Folder 228)
  - McLaughlin - McMicking (Box 38, Folder 229)
  - McMillan - McPherson (Box 38, Folder 230)
  - McGuard - McWilliams (Box 38, Folder 231)
  - Mead - Medd (Box 38, Folder 232)
  - Medicare (Box 38, Folder 233)
  - Meehan - Mellinger (Box 38, Folder 234)
  - Mellon - Myers (Box 38, Folder 235)
  - Micek - Milias (Box 39, Folder 236)
  - Miller (Box 39, Folder 237)
  - Miller, William E. (Box 39, Folder 238)
  - Milligan - Mitchell, Helen C. (Box 39, Folder 239)
  - Mitchell, James P. (Box 39, Folder 240)
  - Mitchell, Joseph - Momberger (Box 39, Folder 241)
  - Monagan - Money (Box 40, Folder 242)
  - Monitor - Mooradian (Box 40, Folder 243)
  - Moore (Box 40, Folder 244)
  - Moorehead - Moravian (Box 40, Folder 245)
  - Mobilization of Republican Enterprise (MORE) (Box 40, Folder 246)
  - Mobilization of Republican Enterprise (MORE) (Box 40, Folder 247)
  - Mobilization of Republican Enterprise (MORE) (Box 40, Folder 248)
  - Morehaus - Morehouse (Box 41, Folder 249)
  - Morris - Mortola (Box 41, Folder 250)
  - Morton - Mosher (Box 41, Folder 251)
  - Moshofsky - Murdock (Box 41, Folder 252)
  - Murphy - Muzika (Box 41, Folder 253)
  - Mydland - Myers (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - M General (Box 41, Folder 0254A)
  - NAACP (National Association for the Advancement of Colored People) - Nail (Box 42, Folder 255)
  - Nair - "National Republican Statesman" (Box 42, Folder 256)
  - "National Review" (Box 42, Folder 257)
  - "National Statesman" - Nullum (Box 42, Folder 258)
  - Nelson - Nevers (Box 42, Folder 259)
  - Newberry - New York Racing Association (Box 42, Folder 260)
  - "New York Report, 1964" (Box 42, Folder 261)
  - "New York Report, 1965" (Box 42, Folder 262)
  - New York State - Young Republicans (Box 42, Folder 263)
  - Nichols - Nirenstein (Box 43, Folder 264)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 43, Folder 265)
    Mostly clippings
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 43, Folder 266)
  - Noble - Noyes (Box 43, Folder 267)
  - Nuclear Testing (Box 43, Folder 268)
  - Nugent - Nygaard (Box 43, Folder 269)
  - National Republican Citizens Committee (Box 44, Folder 270)
  - National Republican Citizens Committee (Box 44, Folder 271)
  - New York City (NYC) [Mayoral] Campaign (Box 44, Folder 272)
  - NYS (New York State) Campaign (Box 44, Folder 273)
  - NYS (New York State) Campaign (Box 44, Folder 274)
  - New York State World's Fair (Box 44, Folder 275)
  - New York State Republican Delegation (Box 45, Folder 276)
  - New York State "Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter" (Box 45, Folder 277)
  - New York State "Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter" (Box 45, Folder 278)
  - New York State "Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter" (Box 45, Folder 279)
  - New York State "Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter" (Box 45, Folder 280)
  - New York State "Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter" (Box 45, Folder 281)
  - New York State "Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter" (Box 45, Folder 282)
  - Oakes - O'Donnell, Gladys (Box 46, Folder 283)
  - O'Donnell, Harry J. (Box 46, Folder 284)
  - O'Donnell, Harry J. (Box 46, Folder 285)
  - O'Donnell, Peter - Ohlendorf (Box 46, Folder 286)
  - O'Kane - Olsson (Box 46, Folder 287)
  - Omlie - Osborn (Box 46, Folder 288)
  - Osteen - Oxberger (Box 46, Folder 289)
  - Pacific - Palgon (Box 47, Folder 290)
  - Palmer (Box 47, Folder 291)
  - Palmquist - Parker, Elizabeth (Box 47, Folder 292)
  - Parker, George W. - Paz (Box 47, Folder 293)
  - Peabody - Peirce (Box 47, Folder 294)
  - Pell - Peper (Box 47, Folder 295)
  - Percy - Perrotta (Box 47, Folder 296)
  - Perry - Petersen (Box 48, Folder 297)
  - Peterson, Arthur R. (Box 48, Folder 298)
  - Peterson (Box 48, Folder 299)
  - Petit - Phillipson (Box 48, Folder 300)
  - Phillpot - Piper (Box 48, Folder 301)
  - Pirkay - Postoway (Box 48, Folder 302)
  - Potter (Box 49, Folder 303)
  - Potts - Poulson (Box 49, Folder 304)
  - Powell (Box 49, Folder 305)
  - Power - Presidential Inauguration (Box 49, Folder 306)
  - Presidential Primaries (Box 49, Folder 307)
  - Presidential Primaries (Box 49, Folder 308)
  - Preston - Propst (Box 49, Folder 309)
  - Prosser - Pyle (Box 49, Folder 310)
  - P General (Box 49, Folder 0310A)
  - Queck - Quist (Box 50, Folder 311)
  - Raad - Ravoira (Box 50, Folder 312)
  - Rawlings - Redman (Box 50, Folder 313)
  - Reece - Reichley (Box 50, Folder 314)
  - Reid - "Reporter Dispatch" (Box 50, Folder 315)
  - Republican - Restifo (Box 50, Folder 316)
  - Resumes (Box 51, Folder 317)
  - Reuben - Reynolds, Frank (Box 51, Folder 318)
  - Reynolds, Grant (Box 51, Folder 319)
  - Reynolds, Hobson - Richards (Box 51, Folder 320)
  - Richardson, Arthur (Box 51, Folder 321)
  - Richardson, Elliot - Ridgely (Box 51, Folder 322)
  - Riegel - Ringstead (Box 51, Folder 323)
  - Ripon Society (Box 52, Folder 324)
  - Risch - Roberts (Box 52, Folder 325)
  - Robertson - Robinson, Kinsey (Box 52, Folder 326)
  - Robinson, R.H. - Rock (Box 52, Folder 327)
  - Rockefeller (Box 52, Folder 328)
  - Rockefeller (Box 52, Folder 0328A)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Bio File (Box 53, Folder 329)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Clippings (Box 53, Folder 330)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Endorsements (Box 53, Folder 331)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Facts, 1964; Republican Platform, 1962; Presidential Primary Results, 1948-1960 (Box 53, Folder 332)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Facts, 1964; Republican Platform, 1962; Presidential Primary Results, 1948-1960 (Box 53, Folder 333)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Issues (Box 53, Folder 334)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Issues (Box 53, Folder 335)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations, 1964, Political Calendar (Box 54, Folder 336)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Invitations, 1964, Political Calendar (Box 54, Folder 337)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Memos, August 1959 - August 1966 (Box 54, Folder 338)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Memos, August 1959 - August 1966 (Box 54, Folder 339)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Press Relations (Box 54, Folder 340)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Press Relations (Box 54, Folder 341)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Press, Radio, TV, and Tape (Box 55, Folder 342)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Remarks, 1964; Space Program, 1964; Critical Issues Papers; Report to Republican National Committee, 1966; Election Summary, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 343)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Republican National Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 55, Folder 344)
    Folder 1 of 3
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Republican National Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 55, Folder 345)
    Folder 2 of 3
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Republican National Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 55, Folder 346)
    Folder 3 of 3
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Schedule, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 347)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - National Campaign Committee (Box 56, Folder 348)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Statements; NAR for President, 1964; Results, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 349)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Statements; NAR for President, 1964; Results, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 350)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Speeches (Box 56, Folder 351)
  - Rockwell - Roffman (Box 56, Folder 352)
  - Rogalin, Wilma C. (Box 56, Folder 353)
  - Rogan - Roll (Box 56, Folder 354)
  - Rollman, Heinz (Box 57, Folder 355)
  - Romack - Romnes (Box 57, Folder 356)
  - Romney, George (Box 57, Folder 357)
  - Romney, Vernon - Rose (Box 57, Folder 358)
  - Rosen - Rosser (Box 57, Folder 359)
  - Rossides - Rowe (Box 57, Folder 360)
  - Rowland - Ryder (Box 57, Folder 361)
  - R General (Box 57, Folder 0361A)
  - Saal - Sandford (Box 57, Folder 362)
  - Sandman - Sayre (Box 58, Folder 363)
  - Scales - Scherwat (Box 58, Folder 364)
  - Schiavone - Schrader (Box 58, Folder 365)
  - Schramm, James (Box 58, Folder 366)
  - Schreiber - Schwaiger (Box 58, Folder 367)
  - Schwalbe, Stuart (Box 58, Folder 368)
  - Schwartz - Schweiker (Box 58, Folder 369)
  - Schwengel, Fred (Box 59, Folder 370)
  - Schwenk - Scola (Box 59, Folder 371)
  - Scott, Hugh (Box 59, Folder 372)
  - Scott, H. Lawrence - Scott, William J. (Box 59, Folder 373)
  - Scranton, William (Box 59, Folder 374)
  - Scranton, William (Box 59, Folder 375)
  - Scribner - Sedlar (Box 59, Folder 376)
  - Seeberg - "Senate Republican Memo" (Box 59, Folder 377)
  - Senate Republican Policy Committee - Shadegg (Box 59, Folder 378)
  - Shaff - Shartzer (Box 60, Folder 379)
  - Shattuck, Edward (Box 60, Folder 380)
  - Shattuck, Edward (Box 60, Folder 381)
  - Shattuck, Edward (Box 60, Folder 382)
  - Shattuck, Frances - Sheeley (Box 60, Folder 383)
  - Sheffield - Shintay (Box 60, Folder 384)
  - Shipley, Carl (Box 60, Folder 385)
  - Shipley, O'Dessa - Shott (Box 61, Folder 386)
  - Showalter - Simms (Box 61, Folder 387)
  - Simmons - Skubitz (Box 61, Folder 388)
  - Slater - Smillie (Box 61, Folder 389)
  - Smith (Box 61, Folder 390)
  - Smith (Box 61, Folder 391)
  - Smylie, Robert (Box 62, Folder 392)
  - Snedcof - Snipes (Box 62, Folder 393)
  - Snodgrass, Robert (Box 62, Folder 394)
  - Snowden - Souser (Box 62, Folder 395)
  - South (Box 62, Folder 396)
  - Southers - Special Groups (Box 62, Folder 397)
  - Special Plans - Spencer (Box 62, Folder 398)
  - Spencer-Roberts, Inc. (Box 62, Folder 399)
  - Speno - Sprague (Box 63, Folder 400)
  - Springer (Box 63, Folder 401)
  - Spurga - Staley (Box 63, Folder 402)
  - Stamler - Steele (Box 63, Folder 403)
  - Steers, Newton I. (Box 63, Folder 404)
  - Steffes - Stephens, Roderick (Box 63, Folder 405)
  - Stephens, Thomas E. (Box 63, Folder 406)
  - Stephenson - Stevens, Robert (Box 63, Folder 407)
  - Stevens, Theodore (Box 64, Folder 408)
  - Stevenson - Stone (Box 64, Folder 409)
  - Stoner - Stranger (Box 64, Folder 410)
  - Street - Sullivan (Box 64, Folder 411)
  - Sullivant - "Syracuse Herald Journal American" (Box 64, Folder 412)
  - S General (Box 64, Folder 0412A)
  - Taber - Taylor (Box 64, Folder 413)
  - Teasley - Thode (Box 65, Folder 414)
  - Thomas - Thompson (Box 65, Folder 415)
  - Thomson - "Time" (Box 65, Folder 416)
  - Timm - Toll (Box 65, Folder 417)
  - Tollefson - Tooker (Box 65, Folder 418)
  - Tool, Jean (Box 65, Folder 419)
  - Toole - Treadway (Box 65, Folder 420)
  - Treadwell - Tribble (Box 66, Folder 421)
  - Tri-Cities Opera - Tupper, Ernest (Box 66, Folder 422)
  - Tupper, Stanley (Box 66, Folder 423)
  - Tupper, Stanley (Box 66, Folder 424)
  - Turcott - Twardy (Box 66, Folder 425)
  - Two-Party System - Tyson (Box 66, Folder 426)
  - T General (Box 66, Folder 0426A)
  - Uihlein - United Presbyterian Church (Box 67, Folder 427)
  - United Republican Finance Committee - Upton (Box 67, Folder 428)
  - Urban Affairs (Box 67, Folder 429)
  - Urion - Utt (Box 67, Folder 430)
  - Vadney - Van Zandt (Box 67, Folder 431)
  - Vardman, Claude (Box 67, Folder 432)
  - Vargas - Vogelman (Box 67, Folder 433)
  - Volpe - Vuccino (Box 67, Folder 0434A)
  - Wachter - Wales (Box 68, Folder 0434B)
  - Walker - Walsh, Richard (Box 68, Folder 435)
  - Walsh, William (Box 68, Folder 436)
  - Walter - Warshawsky (Box 68, Folder 437)
  - Wartolec - Watson, Ruth (Box 68, Folder 438)
  - Watson, Thomas (Box 68, Folder 439)
  - Watson, William - Weed (Box 68, Folder 440)
  - Weeks - Weinstein (Box 68, Folder 441)
  - Weis - Wells, Edward (Box 68, Folder 442)
  - Wells, John (Box 69, Folder 443)
  - Wendell, Harlan (Box 69, Folder 444)
  - Wennar - Wheat (Box 69, Folder 445)
  - Wheatley - Whitehead (Box 69, Folder 446)
  - Whitehouse - Wickens (Box 69, Folder 447)
  - Wickham - Willets (Box 69, Folder 448)
  - Williams (Box 69, Folder 449)
  - Williamson - Wilm (Box 70, Folder 450)
  - Wilson (Box 70, Folder 451)
  - Wilson (Box 70, Folder 452)
  - Wiltsee - Wold (Box 70, Folder 453)
  - Wolf - Woolaway (Box 70, Folder 454)
  - Wooley - Wyman (Box 70, Folder 455)
  - W General (Box 70, Folder 0455A)
  - Xavier (Box 70, Folder 456)
  - Yahn - Yospin (Box 71, Folder 457)
  - Young (Box 71, Folder 458)
  - Young, Fred (Box 71, Folder 459)
  - Younger - Yutin (Box 71, Folder 460)
  - Zaborowski - Zousmer (Box 71, Folder 461)
- State Files and Summaries, 1960-1970; 2; 7.6 Cubic Feet
  This subseries is arranged alphabetically by state.
  The state files consist of letters from individuals arranged by state. There is some duplication of correspondence from the general correspondence between the state files and the general correspondence files in Subseries 1.
  In addition to correspondence, the State Files also contain "trip books" which were prepared by Hinman in advance of a political visit by Governor Rockefeller. The majority of the State Files also contain copies of pages from the "Congressional Quarterly" that denote races in states around the country as well as political notes from that state. The notes contain frequent updates as Hinman interacted with prominent state individuals. The Summaries contain information gathered by Hinman and his staff.
  Both the State Files and Summaries are arranged alphabetically. At the end of the subserires is one file titled, Political Financial Contributors. This file is a list of individuals who pledged monetary support to Governor Rockefeller's political campaigns.
  - State Files - Alabama (Box 72, Folder 462)
  - State Files - Alaska (Box 72, Folder 463)
  - State Files - Arizona (Box 72, Folder 464)
  - State Files - Arkansas (Box 72, Folder 465)
  - State Files - California - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 466)
  - State Files - California - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 467)
  - State Files - California - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 468)
  - State Files - California - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 469)
  - State Files - California - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 470)
  - State Files - California - Hinman Originals (Box 73, Folder 471)
  - State Files - California - Hinman Originals (Box 73, Folder 472)
  - State Files - California - Reports and Polls (Box 73, Folder 473)
  - State Files - California - Reports and Polls (Box 73, Folder 474)
  - State Files - California - "Rockefeller for President" (Box 73, Folder 475)
  - State Files - California - "Rockefeller for President" (Box 73, Folder 476)
  - State Files - California - "Invites" (Box 73, Folder 477)
  - State Files - Colorado (Box 74, Folder 478)
  - State Files - Connecticut (Box 74, Folder 479)
  - State Files - Delaware (Box 74, Folder 480)
  - State Files - District of Columbia - Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 481)
  - State Files - District of Columbia - Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 482)
  - State Files - District of Columbia - "Invites" (Box 74, Folder 483)
  - State Files - Florida (Box 74, Folder 484)
  - State Files - Georgia (Box 75, Folder 485)
  - State Files - Hawaii (Box 75, Folder 486)
  - State Files - Idaho (Box 75, Folder 487)
  - State Files - Illinois (Box 75, Folder 488)
  - State Files - Illinois (Box 75, Folder 489)
  - State Files - Illinois (Box 75, Folder 490)
  - State Files - Indiana (Box 75, Folder 491)
  - State Files - Iowa (Box 76, Folder 492)
  - State Files - Kansas (Box 76, Folder 493)
  - State Files - Kentucky (Box 76, Folder 494)
  - State Files - Louisiana (Box 76, Folder 495)
  - State Files - Maine (Box 76, Folder 496)
  - State Files - Maryland (Box 76, Folder 497)
  - State Files - Massachusetts (Box 77, Folder 498)
  - State Files - Massachusetts (Box 77, Folder 499)
  - State Files - Michigan (Box 77, Folder 500)
  - State Files - Michigan (Box 77, Folder 501)
  - State Files - Minnesota (Box 77, Folder 502)
  - State Files - Mississippi (Box 77, Folder 503)
  - State Files - Missouri (Box 78, Folder 504)
  - State Files - Missouri (Box 78, Folder 505)
  - State Files - Montana (Box 78, Folder 506)
  - State Files - Nebraska (Box 78, Folder 507)
  - State Files - Nevada (Box 78, Folder 508)
  - State Files - New Hampshire - Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 509)
  - State Files - New Hampshire - Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 510)
  - State Files - New Hampshire - "1963 Goldwater and NAR Miscellaneous" (Box 79, Folder 511)
  - State Files - New Hampshire - "1963 Goldwater and NAR Miscellaneous" (Box 79, Folder 512)
  - State Files - New Jersey (Box 79, Folder 513)
  - State Files - New Jersey (Box 79, Folder 514)
  - State Files - New Mexico (Box 79, Folder 515)
  - State Files - New York, Report and Publications - Research Bulletin - "Personal Income in Counties of New York State, 1960" (Box 79, Folder 516)
  - State Files - New York, Report and Publications - Confidential Report - "Political Survey in New York State", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 517)
  - State Files - New York, Report and Publications - "The Moreland Commission on Welfare - Factual Data", 1962 (Box 79, Folder 518)
  - State Files - New York, Report and Publications - "Business Fact Book, 1963 - New York State" (Box 79, Folder 519)
  - State Files - New York, Report and Publications - "United States Census of the Population, 1960, New York", 3 volumes (Box 80, Folder 520)
  - State Files - New York, Report and Publications - "Puerto Ricans in New York" (Box 80, Folder 521)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1961 (Box 80, Folder 0522A)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1962 (Box 80, Folder 0522B)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1963 (Box 80, Folder 523)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1964 (Box 80, Folder 524)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1965 (Box 80, Folder 525)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1965 (Box 80, Folder 526)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1966 (Box 81, Folder 527)
  - State Files - New York, Correspondence - 1967-1970 (Box 81, Folder 528)
  - State Files - North Carolina (Box 81, Folder 529)
  - State Files - North Carolina (Box 81, Folder 530)
  - State Files - North Dakota (Box 81, Folder 531)
  - State Files - Ohio (Box 81, Folder 532)
  - State Files - Oklahoma (Box 81, Folder 533)
  - State Files - Oregon (Box 82, Folder 534)
  - State Files - Oregon (Box 82, Folder 535)
  - State Files - Oregon (Box 82, Folder 536)
  - State Files - Pennsylvania (Box 82, Folder 537)
  - State Files - Puerto Rico (Box 82, Folder 538)
  - State Files - Rhode Island (Box 82, Folder 539)
  - State Files - South Carolina (Box 82, Folder 540)
  - State Files - Texas (Box 82, Folder 541)
  - State Files - Utah (Box 82, Folder 542)
  - State Files - Vermont (Box 82, Folder 543)
  - State Files - Virginia (Box 82, Folder 544)
  - State Files - Virgin Islands (Box 82, Folder 545)
  - State Files - Washington (Box 83, Folder 546)
  - State Files - West Virginia (Box 83, Folder 547)
  - State Files - Wisconsin (Box 83, Folder 548)
  - State Files - Wyoming (Box 83, Folder 549)
  - Summaries - Alabama (Box 83, Folder 550)
  - Summaries - Alaska (Box 83, Folder 551)
  - Summaries - Arizona (Box 83, Folder 552)
  - Summaries - Arkansas (Box 83, Folder 553)
  - Summaries - California (Box 83, Folder 554)
  - Summaries - California (Box 83, Folder 555)
  - Summaries - California (Box 83, Folder 556)
  - Summaries - Colorado (Box 84, Folder 557)
  - Summaries - Connecticut (Box 84, Folder 558)
  - Summaries - Delaware (Box 84, Folder 559)
  - Summaries - District of Columbia (Box 84, Folder 560)
  - Summaries - Florida (Box 84, Folder 561)
  - Summaries - Georgia (Box 84, Folder 562)
  - Summaries - Hawaii (Box 84, Folder 563)
  - Summaries - Idaho (Box 84, Folder 564)
  - Summaries - Illinois (Box 85, Folder 565)
  - Summaries - Illinois (Box 85, Folder 566)
  - Summaries - Indiana (Box 85, Folder 567)
  - Summaries - Indiana (Box 85, Folder 568)
  - Summaries - Iowa (Box 85, Folder 569)
  - Summaries - Kansas (Box 85, Folder 570)
  - Summaries - Kentucky (Box 85, Folder 571)
  - Summaries - Louisiana (Box 86, Folder 572)
  - Summaries - Maine (Box 86, Folder 573)
  - Summaries - Maryland (Box 86, Folder 574)
  - Summaries - Massachusetts (Box 86, Folder 575)
  - Summaries - Michigan (Box 86, Folder 576)
  - Summaries - Minnesota (Box 86, Folder 577)
  - Summaries - Mississippi (Box 86, Folder 578)
  - Summaries - Missouri (Box 86, Folder 579)
  - Summaries - Montana (Box 87, Folder 580)
  - Summaries - Nebraska (Box 87, Folder 581)
  - Summaries - Nevada (Box 87, Folder 582)
  - Summaries - New Hampshire (Box 87, Folder 583)
  - Summaries - New Jersey (Box 87, Folder 584)
  - Summaries - New Jersey (Box 87, Folder 585)
  - Summaries - New Jersey (Box 87, Folder 586)
  - Summaries - New Mexico (Box 87, Folder 587)
  - Summaries - North Carolina (Box 87, Folder 588)
  - Summaries - North Dakota (Box 88, Folder 589)
  - Summaries - Ohio (Box 88, Folder 590)
  - Summaries - Ohio (Box 88, Folder 591)
  - Summaries - Oklahoma (Box 88, Folder 592)
  - Summaries - Oregon (Box 88, Folder 593)
  - Summaries - Oregon (Box 88, Folder 594)
  - Summaries - Pennsylvania (Box 88, Folder 595)
  - Summaries - Pennsylvania (Box 88, Folder 596)
  - Summaries - Puerto Rico (Box 89, Folder 597)
  - Summaries - Rhode Island (Box 89, Folder 598)
  - Summaries - South Carolina (Box 89, Folder 599)
  - Summaries - South Dakota (Box 89, Folder 600)
  - Summaries - Tennessee (Box 89, Folder 601)
  - Summaries - Texas (Box 89, Folder 602)
  - Summaries - Utah (Box 89, Folder 603)
  - Summaries - Vermont (Box 89, Folder 604)
  - Summaries - Virginia (Box 89, Folder 605)
  - Summaries - Virgin Islands (Box 90, Folder 606)
  - Summaries - Washington (Box 90, Folder 607)
  - Summaries - Washington (Box 90, Folder 608)
  - Summaries - West Virginia (Box 90, Folder 609)
  - Summaries - Wisconsin (Box 90, Folder 610)
  - Summaries - Wisconsin (Box 90, Folder 611)
  - Summaries - Wyoming (Box 90, Folder 612)